mawhorter.net 2012-05-02

# Privacy | Elite Iron Workers

At Elite Metal Tools we understand and respect the importance of maintaining your privacy and keeping your information secure. This Privacy Policy and Security Statement shares what information we collect, why we collect it, how we use it, and how we keep your information secure. This Privacy Policy and Security Statement is part of our Terms of Use, which governs your use of elitemetaltools.com. By using elitemetaltools.com you agree to this Privacy Policy & Security Statement and Terms of Use.

**What information do we gather?**

When you order from elitemetaltools.com, we collect the following information: your name, telephone number, e-mail address, billing information (credit card number, expiration date and billing address), products purchased, any relevant promotion code and information (gift certificate redemption code, tradeshow code, etc…) and, if relevant, the recipient's name, address and telephone number. Information you enter is collected even if you cancel or do not complete an order. 

**Why do we collect information?**

Elite Metal Tools strives to provide our customers with quality products and supplies. In addition to that, we strive to provide knowledgeable and friendly service. We gather information to process orders, to enhance and personalize our customers’ shopping experience and to inform our customers and e-mail subscribers of special offers and discounts. 

**How do we use the information?**

We use the information you submit to process your orders (during this process your ship to information may be provided to appropriate manufacture for the purpose of shipping your purchased product; elitemetaltools.com does not guarantee the security of that information), to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience and to inform you of offers and discounts from Elite Metal Tools.

Elite Metal Tools does not sell, trade or rent your e-mail address. We may, on occasion send offers to our customers on behalf of other trusted businesses, but we do not give those businesses your personal information.

In the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets or business of Elite Metal Tools (a "Successor"), one of the assets which would generally be transferred is the information we collect from our customers and site visitors. However, the use of this information by any Successor would still be governed by the terms of this privacy policy, as amended from time to time, including any amendment after such transaction.

We may disclose any information you provide to Elite Metal Tools when we believe disclosure to be appropriate to comply with any law, regulation, governmental request, or to comply with judicial process; or (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate this web site; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Elite Metal Tools, its users, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, or Merchants.

**Links**

Elite Metal Tools wants you to be aware that when you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party Web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies, not ours. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever interacting with, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other website.

**Your Security**

Our web site encrypts your credit card number prior to transmission over the Internet using industry standard secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology. For SSL to work you must use an SSL enabled browser. Most available browsers; version 3.0 and later, support SSL.

However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, we cannot warrant the security of information you transmit to us.

**Your Agreement**

Subject to the above provisions, by using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us and the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change our Privacy from time to time and we will post those changes 30 days prior to their taking effect so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

**Your Feedback**

We welcome feedback concerning this Privacy Policy and Security Statement. Feel free to call or email us.
